Life After Fighting is a action, drama, thriller film directed by Bren Foster.
Retired martial arts world champion Alex Faulkner has settled into a simple life, when the
disappearance of two of his students leads to an unthinkable discovery close to home.
Just when all hope of finding the children is lost, he locates the imprisoned girls and unsurfaces an international
child trafficking operation, which draws him back into the fight of his life against those behind it.
Alex Faulkner, played by Bren Foster.
Samantha Hathaway, played by Cassie Howarth.
Victor Dimov, played by Luke Ford.
Julie Creylan, played by Annabelle Stephenson.
Terry Dimov, played by Anthony Nassif.
Violet Creylan, played by Arielle Jean Foster.
Life After Fighting is a 2024 Australian martial arts film
written, starring and directed by Bren Foster.
The tone is emotional and intense.